Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- 2002 addendum
  - (Box 66)
    - Nelsons - transplant, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2204)
    - Tenth East Senior Center interviews, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2205)
    - 4 Utah: 50 television memories, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2206)
    - New hospital, 1999 September 25; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2207)
    - Immunization, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2208)
    - Carol Kaddas, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2209)
    - Peter Linton-Smith, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2210)
    - Twins right before separation, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2211)
    - X-rays 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2212)
    - Governor Mike Leavitt: State of the State, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2213)
  - (Box 67)
    - Round up, 1995 February 24; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2214)
    - Craiss Pictura's 301, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2215)
    - Gilman, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2216)
    - Mount Olympus bottled water plant, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2217)
    - Toys 4 Tots, 1998 December 23; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2218)
    - American Heart Association dub (heart graphics), 1995 February 02; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2219)
    - Food not bombs, October 10; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2220)
    - Ballot - County Clerk Sherrie Swenson, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2221)
    - Heart monitor - organ donation 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2222)
    - Transplant games, August 23; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2223-2224)
    - Infertility, November 07; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2225)
    - Sandy Filman part 1 - historic television, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2226)
    - Accident (4500 South 200 East), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2227)
    - Pharmacy cover - prescription errors, May 21; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2228)
    - Osteoporosis, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2229)
    - Teen immunization - measles, mumps and rubella 1, March 28; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2230)
    - Dog attacks, August 01; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2231)
    - Roger Colton, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2232)
    - Sandwich generation 1 of 6, October 21; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2233)
    - Knee surgery dub for KTVX, 1995 October 13; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2234)
    - Ultrasound - adoption 23, August 23; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2235)
    - Supplements, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2236)
    - Transplant - Nelsons 2, November 18; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2237)
    - Voting - Salt Lake Community College (SLCC), November 05; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2238)
    - Democratic Convvention 3; Anderson, Owens, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2239)
    - State training school 2, May 19; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2240)
    - X-rays 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2241)
    - Bennett plan, 1993 July 15; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2242)
    - Shriners Hospital cover, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2243)
    - Toothpaste warning 3, 1998 March 24; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2244)
    - Sex offender - Bonneville Correctional, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2245)
    - Sick kids, December 17; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2246)
    - Smoking teens, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2247)
    - Governor Bangerter, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2248)
    - Vegan follow, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2249)
    - Stabb, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2250)
    - Buhler, Vipi, Naley, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2251)
    - Bottled water, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2252)
    - Dentist; water plant, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2253)
    - Testosterone B-10, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2254)
    - Rape crisis 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2255)
    - Democratic electory, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2256)
    - Senate, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2257)
    - Chill audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2258)
    - Welti, July 02; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2259)
    - Sail airplane, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2260-2261)
    - Aerospace museum, 1994 July 06; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2262-2263)
    - Air D-Day 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2264)
    - Sadowski feed, March 10; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2265)
    - Kid skate 2, 1999 October 02; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2266)
    - House; upstairs, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2267)
    - Red Cross 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2268)
    - Juggler 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2269)
    - Trolley 2, 1999 June 10; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2270)
    - Let the pioneering continue, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2271)
    - Pat Shea, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2272)
    - Torrey 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2273)
    - Vault 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2274)
    - 8th Air Force 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2275)
    - Democratic party 1, November 05; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2276)
    - Commerce bank B-roll, 1993 March 16; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2277)
    - Western 8, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2278)
    - B-17 bomber propellers turn, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2279)
    - Red Butte 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2280)
    - S. King interview (stand 1), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2281)
    - Disneyland, 1993 November 18; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2282)
    - Pet resort 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2283)
    - Craig Wirth audio 2, 1995 February 03; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2284)
    - Standups - montage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2285)
  - (Box 68)
    - Mcardy 768, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2286)
    - C-set coming down; x2 going up, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2287)
    - Howard Jorgensen part 1-704, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2288)
    - Unidentified videocassette 760, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2289)
    - Standups - Dennis 12, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2290)
    - New building exteriors 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2291)
    - T-12 Salt Lake City shots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2292)
    - Mark Vrontiki's 706, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2293)
    - Pete Howard, Chief Willaby, cemetery, Jazz 21, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2294)
    - New building, 2000 March 06; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2295)
    - Ed Karl 10, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2296)
    - Howard Jorgensen Part 2-705, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2297)
    - Prison B, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2298)
    - New station exterior B-roll 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2299)
    - Organ 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2300)
    - 30x Wirth reel 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2301)
    - Loom 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2302)
    - Capitol 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2304)
    - Snow removal, 1996 January 29; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2305)
    - 7111-Harris and Love 50th anniversary, old advertisements, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2306)
    - Footage of convention (no audio), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2307)
    - Park City fire 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2308)
    - Call 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2309)
    - News set 9, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2310)
    - Old machines 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2311)
    - Western 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2312)
    - Torleif, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2313)
    - Wirth 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2314)
    - GMS, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2315)
    - VWG coats - segments 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2316)
    - Bloopers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2317)
    - Tribune building cover, Schindler's list, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2318)
    - Ballroom dance 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2319)
    - Great Falls, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2320)
    - Goofy birthday images, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2321)
    - Craig Wirth promos 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2322)
    - Steve Ogden 702, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2323)
    - KTVX News set, 2000 March 01; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2324)
    - Time lapse - 3 Vovo, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2325)
    - B, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2326)
    - Alan Franks commercials 701, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2327)
    - High definition A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2328)
    - Kennecott unusable T-11, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2329)
    - New building off load 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2330)
    - KCPX pictures, 2000 March 06; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2331)
    - Pioneer 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2332)
    - Incomplete Wirth, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2333)
    - Race car 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2334)
    - BD, September 25; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2335)
    - 30X - Siebel 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2336)
    - American Dreams - needs work, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2337)
    - Medical Records, January; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2338)
    - Advance clip for "Not Your Typical Mother", 1998 May 08; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2339)
    - University of Utah medical records 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2340)
    - Nutcracker, 1986; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2341)
    - K-Mart spinner, 1996 July 16; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2342)
    - Reaction 7, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2343)
    - 8th Air Force - 1A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2344)
    - Bing and Bob - CL running footage, 1999; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2345)
    - Helper 19-30, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2346)
    - Marysvale dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2347)
  - (Box 69)
    - TV 2-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2348-2349)
    - TV 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2350)
    - TV 7-11, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2351-2355)
    - TV 13, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2356)
    - TV 15-17, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2357-2359)
    - TV 21-32, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2360-2371)
    - Midvale car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2372)
    - Coca Cola Company "Brake for Surge" promo, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2373)
    - Helper 12, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2374)
    - Panos-Schmitt 20, 97, 39, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2375)
    - For Tiffany Sattelite News: Hollywood cars, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2376)
    - Jon Huntsman: Plant shots with employees, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2377)
    - 30 - auto room BVW 70 - test tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2378)
    - Train station, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2379)
    - 702 - Rerun 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2380)
    - Centennial music, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2381)
    - Adaptec tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2382)
    - Domestic Partner Air, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2383)
    - KTVX: Bounty Hunters, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2384)
    - Movie 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2385)
    - SR deal, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2386)
    - Pony cut down, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2387)
    - AE Murray 129, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2388)
    - Sound storm 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2389)
    - Flower market 2, 1992 February 07; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2390)
    - Few selected shots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2391)
    - Pictures 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2392)
    - Baseball: New York Mets 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2383)
    - Blimp 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2384)
    - Osteoporosis, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2385)
    - CNBC: Navigate 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2386)
    - Best of Best 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2387)
    - 10 B, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2388)
    - Corinthian dub, 1997 July 07; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2389)
  - (Box 70)
    - Utah massage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2390)
    - Massage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2391)
    - Kid ski, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2392)
    - Valentine's Day 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2393)
    - Car, basketball A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2394)
    - Willie car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2395)
    - Craig Trax 20x, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2396)
    - Rubles To Riches, undated; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2397)
    - Rubles To Riches part 2, undated; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2398)
    - Berlin reborn, 1990 June 23; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2399)
    - Rubles To Riches show mix 2, slated, undated; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2400-2401)
    - Utah Auto Expo, October 30; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2402)
    - Legend of Rainbow Bridge, 1996; Audiocassette (Reel 2403)
      Music by November Rain
      Narrator: Charles Phillips
  - (Box 71)
    - Access Software -Margot Kidder, Moon 8, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2304)
    - Wirth special feed: Drive-ins, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2305)
    - Unidentified videocassette 1, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2306)
    - Trade lock-up; Perry, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2307)
    - Jazz basketball game, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2308)
    - Audition, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2309)
    - Paramount Pictures clip reel trailer, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2310)
    - "What is it?" or "Who Cares?", 1982 February 04; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2311)
    - Possible airport sites near Cedar City, 1998 May 01; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2312)
    - Video news release, 1992 September; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2313)
    - Best of Wirth, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 2314)
    - Day the nation cried news clip, undated; 1-inch videotape (Reel 2315)
      President John F. Kennedy (JFK) clip
    - Star promos for 1969-1970 season, Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 2316)
      Station audio closed circuit 12
  - 16mm films (Box 72-73)
    - News, 1959 February; 16mm film (Reel 2317)
    - What is in a name?, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2318)
      Directed by Bob Wells
      Ovaltine
      Johnny Carson
    - News 14, 1953 April 05; 16mm film (Reel 2319)
    - News 9, 1953 March 01; 16mm film (Reel 2320)
    - News 30, 1953 July 26; 16mm film (Reel 2321)
    - NBU News, 1953 April 26; 16mm film (Reel 2322)
    - Unidentified film, 1983 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 2323)
    - Unidentified films, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2324-2331)
    - Hawaii 123, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2332)
    - Balderdash, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2333)
    - Football Parade, 1945; 16mm film (Reel 2334)
    - Road to Nelson Peak, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2335)
    - Fly-in tour 2, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2336)
    - Balderdash at 200, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2337)
    - Different world of Utah - office use only 12, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2338)
    - Beyond the Rainbow - Utah Travil Council, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2339)
    - KTVX Fall sales presentation, undated; 16mm film (Reel 2340)